<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Birthday💕</string>
    <string name="flash">"HAPPY\nBIRTHDAY"</string>
    <string name="selfie">"Finally, I found the prettiest person in the whole goddamn world\n\nHere is a picture of the person and yes this is the best I have ever known"</string>
    <string name="reading">"Below are some random quotes and lines that I wanted to share with you\n"</string>
    <string name="bitwawish">"Hello,Enter your message here"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche">"Enter small special message here"</string>
    <string name="minionWishTrans">"Hello Dear,\n\nI am Kevin. Stuart and Bob are also with me.\n\nWe saw a news headline in the Minions' Daily about the birthday of the cutest person in the world. We know it is you.\n\nWe love you.....We love you more than bananas.\n\nWe would love to come to you for your birthday and yes we want a huge banana party with a banana cake and a banana clown and YOU.\n\nWe were finding ways to contact you then we came across this dude Animesh and he agreed to give our message to you.I wish he doesn't mess things up this time.\n\nWe love you Dear.May God bless you with lots and lots of love and BANANAS.\n\n\n'Hey BOB...BOB don't eat that.Thats not chocolate.Thats poop.Idiot.'\n\n'I'm sorry. Bob keeps doing these things'\n\n'Let me...Let me'\n\n'Okay.Take this'\n\n'Helloooooooo uuummmmmmmmhhhhhhh'\n\n'Happy Birthday...Happy Birthday...Happy Birthday'\n\n'We love you...We love you more than BANANAS'\n\nByeeee...Cyaaa...uuummmmaaaahhh"</string>
    <string name="minionWish">"Bello Dear,\n\ni am lum.  Fouwet yee yok nama bigo com me. \n\nwe ma a daga ripupo een ta minions' rad cama ta oflit de ta cutest pappala een ta globo.  Pem cono pik tis to. \n\nwe ern to. Pem ern to mas pan bananas. \n\nwe polo ern da po da to nunu tu oflit yee si pem quer a hog banana ion com a banana bak yee a banana clown yee to. \n\nwe fem budgan nut da koabo to pen pem lemar bodbag ba dude animesh yee le fibnah da pona noor dogjay da to. Ka jay le hapire mo errec aka ba veela. \n\nwe ern to you. Maybo nos bless to com ism yee ism de ern yee bananas. \n\n\n'hey yok. Yok domo ads pak. Thats non chocolate. Thats poop. Idiot. '\n\n'i'm bido.  Yok par mido les errec'\n\n'let me. Seep me'\n\n'okay. Nupi ba'\n\n'helloooooooo uuummmmmmmmhhhhhhh'\n\n'happy oflit. Fid oflit. Fid oflit'\n\n'we ern to. Pem ern to mas pan bananas'\n\nbyeeee. Cyaaa. uuummmmaaaahhh"</string>
    <string name="dogWishReal">"Bho bhau,\n\naaaaiii aarrrggghhhh bhao bho bhau bhao aargh\n\nargh aaaaaiiiii\n\naaargh bho bho bho bho\n\naaaaiii aarrrggghhhh bhao bho bhau bhao aargh argh aaaaaiiiii\n\naaargh bho bho bho bho\n\naarrrggghhhh bha bho pewpewpew bhow bhow\n\naarrrggghh\n\nbho bho bho hhaarrrggghhhh\n\nbhau bhau bahu bhau babhau bhau aargh argh argh\n\nargh agh aai bhau bhau bhao bho bho bho\n\nBHO BHO"</string>
    <string name="dogWishTrans">"Hello Dear,\n\nMy name is Dogo.\nBut you can call me anything you want.\n\nWell...\n\nYou might know me as I am from your neighbourhood. Me and my friends watch you everyday and make sure no one hurts you.\n\nYes, I am the same light brown coloured dog that sometimes follow you.\n\nYou know when I came to know that your birthday is coming soon, I wanted to wish you,But feared that you might run away thinking I am gonna bite you.\n\nThis wish is made possible because of a very strange phenomena.\n\nThere was this unusual boy who was wandering around your house on a cold evening. I hated him, so me and my friends decided to chase him down so that he never comes back ever. As we were running and following his scooty, all my friends slowly changed their minds and I was left alone in this manhunt. But I quitely followed him to his house and then when the moment came I barked my lungs out.\n\nHe was afraid but strangely and unbelievably we reached to a deal. He promised to make a translator for me. Yes. From bho bho to english.\n\nHe turned out to be a really nice guy. This is all because of him that I am sending my wishes and messages to my best and lovely friend.\n\nDon't ever worry, we are always near you to protect you and to spread our unconditional love.\n\nHave the Happiest Birthday ever.\n\nAnd as humans say, Gali waala sab dekh rha he. We gali waala are watching and protecting you forever.\n\n\nLove."</string>
</resources>
